<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="../../../schemas/song/song_schema_1.0.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<song>
    <metadata>
        <title>Man in Black</title>
        <composer>Johnny Cash</composer>
        <album>Man in Black</album>
        <year>1971</year>
        <genre>Country</genre>
        <notablePerformer>Johnny Cash</notablePerformer>
    </metadata>
    <lyrics>
        <verse>
            <line>Well, you wonder why I always dress in black,</line>
            <line>Why you never see bright colors on my back,</line>
            <line>And why does my appearance seem to have a somber tone.</line>
            <line>Well, there's a reason for the things that I have on.</line>
        </verse>
        <verse>
            <line>I wear the black for the poor and the beaten down,</line>
            <line>Livin' in the hopeless, hungry side of town,</line>
            <line>I wear it for the prisoner who has long paid for his crime,</line>
            <line>But is there because he's a victim of the times.</line>
        </verse>
        <verse>
            <line>I wear the black for those who never read,</line>
            <line>Or listened to the words that Jesus said,</line>
            <line>About the road to happiness through love and charity,</line>
            <line>Why, you'd think He's talking straight to you and me.</line>
        </verse>
        <verse>
            <line>Well, we're doin' mighty fine, I do suppose,</line>
            <line>In our streak of lightnin' cars and fancy clothes,</line>
            <line>But just so we're reminded of the ones who are held back,</line>
            <line>Up front there ought 'a be a Man In Black.</line>
        </verse>
        <verse>
            <line>I wear it for the sick and lonely old,</line>
            <line>For the reckless ones whose bad trip left them cold,</line>
            <line>I wear the black in mournin' for the lives that could have been,</line>
            <line>Each week we lose a hundred fine young men.</line>
        </verse>
        <verse>
            <line>And, I wear it for the thousands who have died,</line>
            <line>Believen' that the Lord was on their side,</line>
            <line>I wear it for another hundred thousand who have died,</line>
            <line>Believen' that we all were on their side.</line>
        </verse>
        <verse>
            <line>Well, there's things that never will be right I know,</line>
            <line>And things need changin' everywhere you go,</line>
            <line>But 'til we start to make a move to make a few things right,</line>
            <line>You'll never see me wear a suit of white.</line>
        </verse>
        <verse>
            <line>Ah, I'd love to wear a rainbow every day,</line>
            <line>And tell the world that everything's OK,</line>
            <line>But I'll try to carry off a little darkness on my back,</line>
            <line>'Till things are brighter, I'm the Man In Black. </line>
        </verse>
    </lyrics>
</song>
